vinyl hekel. Why should I listen to you?
Well,
I used to work with a lady
whose husband was a very eminent
psychologist, and one of the points
that he made was that we're very
well designed to learn fastest
from somebody who's about 18 months
advanced from us, especially when
we're children, and I've only written
one book,
and so I don't know lots of things
about it. I know I've got a lot to
learn. I am determined to
write this second book.
And so kind of like, if you haven't
written a book, maybe it's worth you
listening to me.
There are lots and lots of other
people. I've mentioned a bunch of books
by other people about writing
books, about reading books.
But yes, so I think it would
be great to listen to me.
Nobody has done here tonight in
Edinburgh, but I'm going to post this
online and I'm going to keep going.
I've got an idea. idea. I've got two
ideas for a show for next year.
One of the things that
I'm going to do is
practice the shows in the interim
between now and August next year and
so that they're better. But the
other thing I absolutely need to
do is get better at marketing. Okay,
I'm going to stop there. Thank you
very much. Good night.